Remonda Atef .Net Developer

➤ Remondaa94@gmail.com

(+20) 128 863 8803

• Ain Shams, Cairo

in Remonda Atef | LinkedIn

RemondaAtef | Github

Profile

A Full Stack .NET Developer with 2 years of experience. Seeking a challenging role to utilize my technical skills through an organization that encourages my continuous development, in which I can interact and work efficiently to improve myself.

Professional Experience

2022/10 - present Full Stack .NET Developer, Integrated Business Solutions Company- OnSite

IBS is a leading company that provides corporate checks printing software solutions and bank loan software system solutions.

Convert vb.net desktop applications to web applications.

Modify and maintain .net 4.7.2 MVC web application to .net core MVC 8 and use clean

architecture.

Make Microservices Projects, .NET Core projects, .NET MVC projects, Windows Apps, .NET Web API Projects, Windows Service Projects, Visual Basic Projects, and Android

Apps.

2022/10 - 2023/01 Web Development internship, The sparks Foundation- Remote

Make a Basic Banking System

2022/03 – 2022/04 .NET Internship, Algoriza Company- Remote

Learning C#, Database SQL server, LINQ, EF, Dot net core, Web API, Onion

architecture.

Education

2018 – 2022 computers and artificial intelliegence

Helwan University

GPA: 2.95/4.00 Very Good

Graduation Project grade: Excellent A+

Skills

Technical Skills

C#, SQL Server

ASP.Net MVC, ASP.Net Core, ASP.Net Web API,

vb.net

LINQ, EF Core,

C, Python

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, jQuery, JSON

Flutter

Soft Skills

Teamwork Self-learner

Ambition

L, Coo, Javascript, Dootstrap, JQuery, Joorv

Concepts

Object Oriented Programming (OOP)

Problem-Solving SOLID Principles Design patterns Clean Architecture

Tools

Visual Studio 2019, Visual Studio 2022, Visual Studio

Code

ms SQL server 2016, ms SQL server 2022

Android Studio, Postman

My Graduation Project (Custodies Management System)

using .NET Core API

that transformed the process of managing custodies in the inventory to an electronic way and managed. This project helped to reduce dealing with vast amounts of papers and queues.

Payroll System

Web application using .NET Framework 4.7.2 and ASP.NET MVC.

Manages the calculations of employees' salaries and advances.

Includes features for tracking base salary, overtime, bonuses, and deductions and generates detailed reports for both employees and management.

Customer Requests System

Web application using .NET Framework 4.7.2 and ASP.NET MVC

Import customers and export requests as CSV or XML files.

Using Kendo Grid and RDLC reports.

Using a QR scanner to insert the QR data into the database.

Accounting & Stores System

Web application using .NET Framework 4.7.2 and ASP.NET MVC

Accounting System

Microservices web application from scratch using .NET 5

.NET web app connect with Windows Service

Make Print of PrintDocument from windows service and publich web app to IIS

Image comparison Windows App

using C#

find the percentage difference between the two images. and apply this in web application also.

Image Quality Assurance Windows App

using C#

get Lenght, Height, Darkness, Skew, Record Size, and Noise of an image.

and compare these values with the values I have to know if the image has a problem or not

Attendance Flutter App

Integrate fingerprint and faceprint authentication, and call backend .NET APIs.

Basic Banking System

using .NET Core MVC

Create a simple dynamic website to transfer money between multiple customers, and deploy it in the Azure server.

Address book project

using .NET Core API

Manage CRUD operations.

Handwritten English letters using Artificial Neural Network (Python)